<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Research-experiences on Portfolio</title>
    <link>http://tongzhengregen.cn/research-experience/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Research-experiences on Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-Hans</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 22:02:40 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://tongzhengregen.cn/research-experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Narrative and Space: Reconstruction of South China Historical Trail Heritage Network</title>
      <link>http://tongzhengregen.cn/research-experience/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tongzhengregen.cn/research-experience/first/</guid>
      <description>叙事与空间
——南粤古驿道遗产网络构建研究
LI Mengran, ZHENG Tong, TANG Chuqiao, LIU Longying, SU Yanni, LIANG Xiyue, LI Hui
李梦然 1 ，郑 潼 2 ，汤楚乔 3 ，刘龙英 4 ，苏燕妮 5 ，梁浠玥 6，李 晖 7
ABSTRACT Nanyue Ancient Path is the communication route between Lingnan and foreign regions, and has existed across periods throughout history. It is also known as the population migration corridor, the commodity exchange route and an ancient path making possible cultural exchange between civilizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>稽俗振今，众治兴村： 后乡土社会下乡村文化治理的实践与反思 ——基于连州市保安村的调查研究</title>
      <link>http://tongzhengregen.cn/research-experience/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 18:15:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tongzhengregen.cn/research-experience/second/</guid>
      <description>Abstract China&amp;rsquo;s rural areas are in the transition period from &amp;ldquo;rural society&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;post-rural society&amp;rdquo;, and cultural governance is the countryside. The key to the breakthrough of village development. How to absorb the wisdom of rural cultural governance and find the endogenous driving force of rural cultural development, Exploring the experience of rural cultural governance is an important issue that needs to be solved at present. The report focuses on the governance of rural culture Comprehensive investigation, taking Baoan Village in Lianzhou City, Guangdong Province as an example, for a 3-year investigation and study.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Belief Space Features and Renewal Strategies of Jieyang Ancient City揭阳古城信仰空间特征及更新策略</title>
      <link>http://tongzhengregen.cn/research-experience/third/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 18:16:27 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tongzhengregen.cn/research-experience/third/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Spiritual spaces play an important role as communal spaces in everyday life. They are important carriers of historical, cultural, and community relations in the ancient city as well as a focal point for the revitalization of the city. Throughout its long history of urban development, the ancient area of Jieyang City has served not only as a geographical space, but also as a spiritual space, creating and preserving a legacy of human creativity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study On Ecological Restoration And Landscape Improvement Technology Along Historical Trail In Northern Guangdong</title>
      <link>http://tongzhengregen.cn/research-experience/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 22:02:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tongzhengregen.cn/research-experience/4/</guid>
      <description>粤北古驿道沿线生态修复及景观提升技术研究</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
